<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Chennai Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="nav_name">Places to Visit</string>
    <string name="restaurant">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="theatres">Theatres</string>
    <string name="beaches">Beaches</string>
    <string name="malls">Malls</string>
    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="beach1">Marina</string>
    <string name="beach1_add">Marina Beach, Triplicane, Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India</string>
    <string name="beach1_img1">marina1</string>
    <string name="beach1_img2">marina2</string>
    <string name="beach1_desc">Marina Beach is a natural urban beach in the city of Chennai (Madras), India, along the Bay of Bengal. The beach runs from near Fort St. George in the north to Foreshore Estate in the south, a distance of 6.0 km (3.7 mi), making it the longest natural urban beach in the country.</string>
    <string name="beach2">Elliots Beach</string>
    <string name="beach2_add">Elliots Beach, Besant Nagar, Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India</string>
    <string name="beach2_img1">elliot1</string>
    <string name="beach2_img2">elliot2</string>
    <string name="beach2_desc">Elliots Beach (popularly known as "Besant Nagar Beach" or "Bessie") is located in Besant Nagar, Chennai, India. It forms the end-point of the Marina Beach shore and is named after Edward Elliot, onetime chief magistrate and superintendent of police, Madras. It has the Velankanni Church and the Ashtalakshmi Kovil nearby.</string>
    <string name="beach3">Tiruvottiyur Beach</string>
    <string name="beach3_add">Tiruvottiyur Kuppam, Appar Nagar, Tiruvottiyur, Chennai, Tamil Nadu 600019, India</string>
    <string name="beach3_img1">tiruvottiyur1</string>
    <string name="beach3_img2">tiruvottiyur2</string>
    <string name="beach3_desc">Tiruvottiyur (Thiruvottriyur or TVT) is a neighbourhood in North Chennai administered by the Greater Chennai Corporation. It is part of the Tondiarpet division, located to the north of Chennai city. It is one of the 15 administrative zones in Greater Chennai Corporation. The zone is named to be Zone 1 (Tiruvottiyur). Due to its proximity to Parrys and Chennai Central along with comparatively cheaper residential space and decent amenities, it is fast becoming a sought after residential destination.</string>
    <string name="mall1">Phoenix Marketcity</string>
    <string name="mall1_add">142, Velachery Main Road, Velachery, Chennai, Tamil Nadu 600042, India</string>
    <string name="mall1_desc">Phoenix Market City (Chennai) is a shopping mall developed by Phoenix Mills Limited located in Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India. It was opened in January 2013 and is the 2nd largest mall in the city.</string>
    <string name="mall2">Chennai Citi Centre</string>
    <string name="mall2_add">No.10 11, Dr.Radhakrishnan Salai, Loganathan Colony, Mylapore, Chennai, Tamil Nadu 600004, India</string>
    <string name="mall2_desc">The Chennai Citi Centre is a shopping mall in Mylapore, Chennai, India. It opened on 3 March 2006 and is located on Radhakrishnan Salai. According to Cushman and Wakefield, a global real estate consultancy firm, it is one of the most expensive shopping malls in Chennai.</string>
    <string name="mall3">Spencer Plaza</string>
    <string name="mall3_add">768 769, Anna Salai, Chennai, Tamil Nadu 600002, India</string>
    <string name="mall3_desc">Spencer Plaza is a shopping mall located on Anna Salai in Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India, and is one of the modern landmarks of the city</string>
    <string name="mall4">The Forum Vijaya</string>
    <string name="mall4_add">NSK Salai, Arcot Road, Vadapalani, Chennai, Tamil Nadu 600026, India</string>
    <string name="mall4_desc">Forum Vijaya Mall is a shopping mall located in Vadapalani, Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India, developed by Prestige Group. This mall is spread over 6,36,000 square feet of retail space. More than 100 shops occupy its four floors</string>
    <string name="restaurant1">Annalakshmi Restaurant</string>
    <string name="restaurant1_add">18 3 Rukmani Lakshmipathy Road Sigapi Achi Building,1st floor, Adjacent to Raja Muthaiya, Rani Meyammai Hall, Chennai, Tamil Nadu 600008, India</string>
    <string name="restaurant1_desc">Temple-themed vegetarian restaurant offering northern and southern Indian and Jain cuisine.</string>
    <string name="restaurant2">The Marina</string>
    <string name="restaurant2_add">39, College Road, Nungambakkam, Chennai, Tamil Nadu 600006, India</string>
    <string name="restaurant2_desc">Environmentally-conscious restaurant plating sustainable Indian and Chinese style fish and seafood.</string>
    <string name="restaurant3">Fusilli Reasons</string>
    <string name="restaurant3_add">2/64, Ormes Rd, Kilpauk, Chennai, Tamil Nadu 600010, India</string>
    <string name="restaurant3_desc">Tiny, laid-back eatery turning out an array of garlic breads and pastas, along with nachos.</string>
    <string name="restaurant4">Little Italy</string>
    <string name="restaurant4_add">No 112, Eldorado Building, Nungambakkam High Road,, Chennai, Tamil Nadu 600034, India</string>
    <string name="restaurant4_desc">Chic contemporary chain dining room for traditional Italian food, gelato and some Mexican dishes.</string>
    <string name="theatre1">SPI Cinemas - Sathyam</string>
    <string name="theatre1_add">8, Thiru Vi Ka Road, Royapettah, Chennai, Tamil Nadu 600014, India</string>
    <string name="theatre1_desc">Cinema and entertainment complex with a cafe, theatre and patisserie as well as video games.</string>
    <string name="theatre2">SPI Escape Multiplex</string>
    <string name="theatre2_add">Express Avenue Mall, Whites Rd, Express Estate, Royapettah, Chennai, Tamil Nadu 600014, India</string>
    <string name="theatre2_desc">SPI Cinemas is a leading player in the entertainment industry offering services such as exhibition, distribution and production. SPI Cinemas strives to be at the forefront of media technology and endeavours to bring new entertainment technology to customers first.</string>
    <string name="theatre3">Ega Multiplex</string>
    <string name="theatre3_add">810, Poonamallee High Road, Vasu Street, Kilpauk, Chennai, Tamil Nadu 600010, India</string>
    <string name="theatre3_desc">Standard cinema with air conditioning offering an array of movies and a snack counter.</string>
    <string name="theatre4">AGS Cinemas - Villivakkam</string>
    <string name="theatre4_add">No.1/1, Mettu Street, Behind Bus Depot, Villivakkam, Chennai, Tamil Nadu 600049, India</string>
    <string name="theatre4_desc">Modern movie theatre with a loyalty scheme, showing their own productions and other Hindi films.</string>
</resources>
